http://www.gosafeguard.com/privacy-policy.asp

If you have trouble accessing content on our website, please call (855) 778-3124 or email customerservice@gosafeguard.com for assistance.
Order Requests (0)
Learn & Grow
Ideas, How To's,
Product Catalog
Home »
Privacy Policy
Safeguard Privacy Policy
Click here for PRIVACY NOTICE – CALIFORNIA-SPECIFIC ADDENDUM
Protecting privacy is an important part of the business of Safeguard. Throughout our existence, we have been a trusted custodian of sensitive data. Our customers rely on that trust. We have a long history of recognizing and protecting the privacy of our customers' information. In 1999 we formalized our privacy policy to ensure that all customers understand our commitment to protecting their privacy. We are committed to protecting privacy and utilizing technology that gives you the safest and most powerful online experience available. We want to assure you that when we ask for customer information, our goal is to improve our business customer relationships and provide solutions you need to grow your business.The gosafeguard site is directed or intended for U.S. business customers only. This Privacy Policy is effective October 1, 2009 and applies to all customer-identifiable information we obtain when a business customer visits and uses this Web site.Through this site, Safeguard provides a variety of solutions to businesses large or small through its channel of independent contractors we refer to as "Distributors." The Safeguard site enables the ordering of products and services that include business cards and stationery; business check printing; employee apparel; promotional products; retail supplies; business signs; and marketing services. The following statements will help you understand how we collect, use, and safeguard the information you provide through our Web sites. The terms "we," "our," and "us" in this Privacy statement refer to Safeguard and its affiliates, subsidiaries and agents.Information Collection & UseWe are committed to protecting your business information. We use the information collected about you to process orders and to provide a more personalized shopping experience. We may also use your information to communicate with you about products, services and future promotions. For the purposes of order verification and fraud prevention, we exchange information about our customers internally and among our affiliates. This Web site uses cookies to improve your shopping experience. The information stored in cookies helps us serve you better by keeping track of your orders, and improve your online experience.The type of information we collect, use, or share may depend on the product or service you have with us. At times, we may request that you voluntarily supply identifying information for purposes such as receiving correspondence, registering on this Web site, making purchases, or participating in online surveys or market research. If you elect to participate, we may require you to provide business information, including your name, mailing address, phone number, financial institution information, credit card information, or email address. When you submit business information to us, you understand and agree that we and our affiliates may access, store, and use your information.lnformation you provide will be protected according to our strict standards of security and confidentiality. Safeguard recognizes and appreciates the importance of responsible use of the information you choose to provide. We do not share email addresses with unaffiliated third parties for marketing purposes without your express consent.Information DisclosureSafeguard may selectively share customer information, including names and mailing addresses, with reputable third parties and organizations whose products and services we think may interest you if the customer information is independently obtained by us (that is, if the information is received from sources other than your financial institution).Names and other information that are received by us through a financial institution are not provided to non-affiliated third parties except for the purpose of fulfilling our contracts and commitment with financial institutions or as otherwise permitted by law. We take steps to require that our vendors, consultants, suppliers, and contractors observe our Privacy Policy with respect to security and the collection, use, and exchange of our customers' information. They are expected to abide by the Privacy Policy when working with us.We provide you with the opportunity to opt out of receiving unsolicited marketing mail as a result of your transaction with us or authorizing us to share your personal information with unaffiliated third parties and other organizations. Please see "To Correct/Update/Access/Opt Out" below for contact information regarding your choice to opt out.Online Privacy & SecuritySecurity measures are in place on this Web site to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. We offer industry-standard security measures available through your Web browser. When you are on this Web site, the information you provide is encrypted and scrambled en route and decoded once it reaches us. Please remember that email, which is different from the encrypted sessions above, is not secure. Therefore, we ask that you do not send confidential information such as credit card or account numbers to us via an unsecured email message.When you browse this Web site, you do so without revealing your identity. Personal information is not collected without your awareness. For each visitor to this Web site, our servers recognize the Web site you came from and the Web site you visit after you leave. In the order-capture and site registration process, we may track the order preferences of visitors to the Web site, by using cookies.Security & CookiesCookies are small pieces of information that are stored by your Web browser on your computer's hard drive. A cookie may contain information (such as a unique user session ID) that is used to track the pages of the Web sites you've visited. We use cookies, but we do not store sensitive information, other than your name, in your cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can set your browser to decline cookies. Even if your Web browser is set to decline cookies, you can use many of the features within this site.You may choose to register online, by sharing your information and ordering preferences for future purchases. lnformation you provide will be safeguarded according to our strict standards of security and confidentiality.Children Visiting Our Web SitesThis Web site is directed at adults. We do not knowingly collect or use information from children. Should children access this Web site, we are confident that parents will not judge any of the information provided as objectionable for viewing. If you are under 18, you may use this Web site only with the involvement of a parent or guardian.Other Web Sites Linked to Safeguard's Web SiteWe are committed to offering the products and services you need to grow and manage your business. We offer services through relationships with third-party providers. This Web site will provide secure links to these third-party providers as a part of the Safeguard shopping experience. Please review applicable terms, conditions and privacy policies displayed on the third-party provider Web sites. In most cases, links to other Web sites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to the users of this Web site. We are not responsible for the content or information practices employed by other Web sites that are linked to or from this Web site.Understanding Terms, Changes and How to Contact UsBy using this Web site, you consent to our posted Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, please do not use this Web site. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this policy at any time. Your continued use of this Web site following the posting of changes to these terms means that you accept these changes.We may change our privacy policy at any time. Any changes to the privacy and security policy will be posted on this Web site so that you are aware of the information we collect, how we use it, as well as the latest update on how we maintain the secure portions of our Web site.Periodically, our operations and business practices are reviewed for compliance with corporate policies and procedures governing the confidentiality of information. These reviews are conducted by internal staff who report directly to Safeguard management, external auditing and accounting firms, and government regulators. Included in these self-assessments and examinations are reviews of the controls and safeguards described in our Privacy Policy.We are committed to ensuring that the information we obtain and use about our customers is accurate. You can help us maintain accurate records by informing us of changes or modifications to your personal information using one of the methods listed under Contacting Safeguard. Our service representatives are trained to answer questions about and give you reasonable access to your personal information in our database.To Correct/Update/Access/Opt Out:Safeguard1010 W. Mockingbird Lane, Suite #100Dallas, TX 75247Phone: (800) 523-2422Fax: (800) 439-8423Email: customerservice@gosafeguard.comFor General Inquiries:If you have questions regarding this Privacy Policy, the practices of our Web sites, or your dealings with our Web sites, please contact us at:Safeguard Business Systems, Inc.General Counsel1010 W. Mockingbird Lane, Suite #100Dallas, TX 752471-800-523-2422 ext. 443927If more information is needed, help is available though the Safeguard Legal Department and atcustomerservice@gosafeguard.com
Talk to Safeguard
(855) 778-3124
There are 600+ Safeguard representatives in the U.S. and Canada. One is ready to serve you today.
© 2020 Safeguard Business Systems, Inc. Safeguard and the centurion head design are registered trademarks of Safeguard Business Systems, Inc. All other logos are the intellectual property of their respective owners.
Products & Services
Business Checks
Business Forms
Office Supplies
Online Marketing & Web Services
Printed Products
Design & Print Services
Promotional Products & Apparel
Copyright Infringement (DMCA)
